[{
    "theme": "⚽ En un partido de fútbol - Final de la UEFA en Glasgow",
    "langread": "en",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "How do you ask 'How are you?' to a fan?",
            "answers": ["¿Qué tal estás?", "¿Cómo estás?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'What's your name?'",
            "answers": ["¿Cómo te llamas?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'Where are you from?'",
            "answers": ["¿De dónde eres?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'We are from Seville'?",
            "answers": ["Somos de Sevilla"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'Who is going to win tonight?'",
            "answers": ["¿Quién va a ganar esta tarde?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you confidently say 'Sevilla, without a doubt'?",
            "answers": ["Sevilla, sin duda"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Referee is biased'?",
            "answers": ["Árbitro casero"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Offside'?",
            "answers": ["Fuera de juego"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask if it is someone's first time in Scotland?",
            "answers": ["¿Es la primera vez que estás en Escocia?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'The people are very friendly'?",
            "answers": ["La gente es muy amable"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'The city is very clean'?",
            "answers": ["La ciudad está muy limpia"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you cheer 'Come on!'?",
            "answers": ["¡Venga!"]
        },
        {
            "question": "What do you shout when your team scores a goal?",
            "answers": ["¡Gol!"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Champions'?",
            "answers": ["Campeones"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'It's very important, football in Spain'?",
            "answers": ["Es muy importante el fútbol en España"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'It's the most important sport'?",
            "answers": ["Es el deporte más importante"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you name two of the most important teams in Spain?",
            "answers": ["Madrid y Barcelona"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Many Spaniards go to the stadiums'?",
            "answers": ["Muchos españoles van a los estadios"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I suppose so'?",
            "answers": ["Supongo que sí"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'The stadiums are almost always full'?",
            "answers": ["Los estadios casi siempre están llenos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'For example, Madrid, Barcelona, Sevilla'?",
            "answers": ["Por ejemplo, Madrid, Barcelona, Sevilla"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Today it's raining'?",
            "answers": ["Hoy llueve"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'There was good weather yesterday'?",
            "answers": ["Ayer hizo buen tiempo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'goal' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["el gol"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'referee' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["el árbitro"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'stadium' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["el estadio"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'ball' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["el balón"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'team' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["el equipo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'player' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["el jugador"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'fans/supporters' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["la afición"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'coach' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["el entrenador"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'scoreboard' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["el marcador"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'penalty' in Spanish?",
            "answers": ["el penalti"]
        }
    ]
}]
